# CHANDRAPRAKASH KANTALAL YADAV (M.Com)

Age: 34 Years, Experience: 11 Years

**Email-** ckyadav88@gmail.com **Contact No.** 090330 79661 070167 87851



# **KNOW MYSELF**

Date of Birth: 1st January, 1988Fathers Name: Kantalal P. Yadav

Marital Status: Unmarried

> Permanent Address: 4, Jay Shree Mahakali Nagar, B/H: Parimal Hospital, Opp. Gujarat Stadium, Sabarmati, Ahmedabad -380005 Gujarat

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

I am Skilled Accounting Professional with 10 + Years of experience, currently working as Senior Officer Accounts & Finance. I have Strong understanding of all concepts of accounting, finance, & Taxation. I have ability to manage multiple assignments (Multi-Tasking) while meeting tight deadlines schedules. I possess reputation as a self-directed professional with excellent problem solving, analytical and communication skills. I have proven track record of performing work in an ethical manner while consistently maintaining the integrity of financial data. I have strong relationship-building skills and effective collaboration with management, co-workers, vendors and clients. My interested Careers are Accounting & Taxation (GST & Income Tax), I am also interested in Corporate Finance, Fund raising, Budget & Cash Flow Management with growth-oriented Organization repute.

#### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Examination	University/Board	Year	Class Obtained
M.com	Gujarat University	2014	Second Class
B.com	Gujarat University	2008	Second Class
H.S.C.	Gujarat Board	2005	First Class
S.S.C.	Gujarat Board	2003	Second Class

## **COMPUTER PROFICIENCY**

- > Well conversant with Microsoft Windows XP, Windows 7, MS Outlook.
- > MS-Excel, MS-Word, MS-PowerPoint, Well Versed with Internet Fundamental.
- Following Accounting Software well versed with:
  - 1) SAP FICO Module
  - 2) Tally ERP9
  - 3) Quick Book

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Name of Company: Sanghi Industries Limited Period: April 2019 to till date

**Designation:** Senior Officer Accounts & Finance

Industry: Cement Manufacture

#### **Major Roles & Responsibilities includes:**

- > TDS & TCS working & payment on monthly basis, Quarterly TDS & TCS Return.
- Issue Form 16, 16A & 27D file Form 15CA & 15CB
- > TDS payment entry with ledger clearing at regular interval.
- Ledger scrutiny
- > Handling Payroll Compliance: PF, ESIC, Prof. Tax
- > Profitability Statement, Daily Sales Report
- Budget vs Actual MIS and Other costing related MIS

- Assisting auditors & HOD Accounts in Finalization of accounts, Tax Audit, Income Tax Return.
- ➤ Good Knowledge of Accounts Payable & Accounts Receivable
- > Filing of GST Returns (GSTR3B & GSTR1)Reconciling ITC with Books

Name of Company: The Sandesh Limited

Period: October 2014 to March 2019
Designation: Senior Accounts Executive

Industry: News-Media

## **Major Roles & Responsibilities includes:**

- Preparation of Monthly Balance Sheet and submission to GM of Accounts & Group CFO.
- > Provision and Prepaid details preparation and uploading on monthly basis.
- > TDS & TCS working & payment on monthly basis, Quarterly TDS & TCS Return.
- > TDS payment entry with ledger clearing at regular interval.
- ➤ Day to day accounting entries for Vendor bill booking, Cash Expense booking with due consideration of legal compliance like TDS, Service Tax include RCM, GST (Goods & Service Tax).
- > Payment of Salary to employees and vendor payment.
- Prepare budget sheet, Check budget variance and changes with approval.
- > Bank Reconciliation in SAP
- > Liaison with bankers, Inter-Department and with Statutory / Internal Auditors.
- > Assisting auditors and GM Accounts in Finalization of accounts, Tax Audit, Income Tax Return.
- > Any other details as required by management and submission to management as required.
- Posting of customer invoice & Credit Note Telecast Division

Name of Company: Axiom BPM Services Pvt. Ltd. Period: March 2012 to September 2014

**Designation:** Accounts Executive

Industry: IT

## Major Roles & Responsibilities includes:

- Engaged in the accounting of the company, group companies and personal accounts of Directors.
- > Handling Bills Receivables & Bills Payable.
- > Generation of MIS Reports.
- > Liaisoning with the Labour Law officers and Govt. Departments viz. ESIC, EPF.
- > Dealing with the Bankers for Corporate Payroll Bank Accounts, FIRC and other related matters.
- > Calculation of TDS, Service Tax & Profession Tax and ensuring timely payment.

Name of Company: Rainbow Papers Limited

Period: August 2009 to September 2010

Designation: Sales Assistant Industry: Paper Manufacture

#### Major Roles & Responsibilities includes:

- > Handling Excise Invoices and Challans.
- > Daily Dispatch Arrangement.
- Network Planning and Execution.
- > Handling Stock, Finished Goods and B.S.R. Reports.
- Maintain Stock Verification and checking.

#### **SKILLS**

- Good Analytical & Inter-personal abilities.
- Keen learner with constant zest to acquire new skills.

#### **HOBBIES**

Listening Music, Cricket, Travelling.